

CONTACT

- +383 46 144 653
- Drenas, Kosova 13000
- https://mendritmiftari.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

2019 UNIVERSITY OF BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY (UBT)

 Bachelor - Computer Science and Engineering

2015 - 2018 PROFESSIONAL SCHOOL "FEHMI LLADROVCI"

• Middle School - Computer Science

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS, SASS, LESS
- PHP
- ReactJS
- GraphQL
- C#
- Asp.net
- SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL

LANGUAGES

- English (Intermediate)
- German (Basics)
- Albanian (Fluent)

MENDRIT MIFTARI

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

A web developer with over a year of experience in React and Typescript. Worked on the PABAU web application, improving features, fixing bugs, and ensuring everything runs smoothly. Familiar with using GraphQL APIs for data handling and extending UI components with Ant Design. Built React components from scratch and used tools like Jest, Cypress, and Playwright to test and make sure the application works well.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pabau LLC

Software Developer

MAY 2023 - JULY 2024

- Developed and enhanced features for the PABAU web application, utilizing Typescript within the Next.js React framework.
- Fixed bugs and improved existing features, ensuring high-quality and reliable application performance.
- Integrated GraphQL APIs, facilitating efficient data fetching and manipulation.
- Extended and reused components from Ant Design, ensuring consistency and efficiency in the UI.
- Built modern React components from scratch, adhering to best practices and optimizing for performance and scalability.
- Conducted comprehensive testing using Jest, Cypress, and Playwright to ensure robust and reliable application functionality.

KosovaOutSource LLC Front End Web Developer

February 2022 -August 2022

- Developed front-end user interfaces for several complex web applications with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Utilized React frameworks to create interactive, responsive, and userfriendly web designs.
- Optimized websites for maximum speed and scalability, while also ensuring compatibility with various browsers and devices.
- Created custom UI components and implemented layouts using HTML5, CSS3 (SASS), and JavaScript.

REFERENCE

References available on request